our final inductee of the evening will a
Sri Sri not a remarkable individual here
to speak about him as Rama shot also a
remarkable individual but that's just
one of the leaders of the association of
Indian physicians of northern Ohio and
that well all that didn't explain one of
his passions as a medical doctor and
that's basically a mission under the
umbrella of that association where
they've reached out to the poor in the
destitute in developing countries offer
aid
one example of this was a 2001
earthquake in India where during one of
those got remissions they matched about
hundreds of villagers their primary
health care dental I care free medicines
and eyeglasses this is what they do
this is he he's introducing trees
[Applause]
community from Ravenna Ohio and the
social position when Kenyatta
letter in order to there was a DC and
North educational achievement which are
listed in the firmament we are because
it's awesome
contradiction is making to entire Sarah
International Organization survival
canister as 3100 spread voltage hero
person in the United States and other
major cities and 21 countries horses Wow
the Spirit is awesome
mr. guinea Simha organism Sanskrit word
seven means selfless service without any
destination
what does every seventh innumerous
polish services in 25 disasters in
registers for God tells us not know and
bonuses in Australia India UK Canada
only on
[Music]
listen Sonny
each to nest
what to
[Music]
this viral and when they presented to
phonetic 400 he also shares and consults
his talents and expertise with so many
developing countries on the sea of water
ready and poised even with full-time job
as a computer science and Gemini program
the a spectrum also disposal with 22
countries with different times hours
ahead and some random countries are
[Music]
[Applause]
Irish when they thought - she remembers
god I wish it was all the truth the
truth is really Sarah International is a
volunteer-based organization I just
pretend to work on this working I think
the tradition I get to speak so much I
am very very indebted to the tan in them
or making this happen is one of them
forgiving somebody who's been in this
community for 31 years since it's very
much
I came to Cleveland in spite of the data
and to my
[Applause]
[Music]
today so so the second industrial
actually is about there was a honey like
a disaster place in southern India in
August 2018 so
setup with our sister organization in
which L v12 worketh in India we have
three million people in the United
States so this particular Street sliver
of the western part the southern part of
India so Kara so this is good cause like
okay fine you send that information loss
established lives with the Indian Navy
and Air Force which was thinking well
not 856 p.m. this is exact CST August 18
recap the following message please help
no response from authorities on top no
food no water softening medical
treatment please to rescue operations in
this area we got this from our
surveillance another one in Houston
songs she believes he contacted our
flight back to the Navy and within four
hours rescuer action success know they
are safe they may be tested as possible
so this is the way 10,000 months try
Travis I made people talk about the fact
is about social media
social behavior
and first I'll talk to you about
and we already with the athletes when
they coach who is a volunteerism
so Jeff well this is yours and we have
put together the program a linear
speed-up children so we get students
from Case Western Reserve
community here okay we had 74 students
and this year about 20 of them graduated
from high school when they were doing
these events in a semester they were
able to get a simpie they got this
college scholarships I am going to part
two of them are being pursued by IVs
this is fantastic Society no poverty
cost it cost as two hundred and fifty
dollars per student because we do the
supervision of what is to the super
million reading the harbor and the our
students you know collecting the pieces
that's what you guys and we are blessed
with fantastic volunteers and donors
like you who support us thank you
[Applause]